[
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called /hector_map_server/get_distance_to_obstacle_xbl?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called /hector_map_server/get_distance_to_obstacle_xyr?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called hector_map_server_xhd?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called hector_object_tracker_xii?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called worldmodel/image_percept_xed?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called hector_object_tracker?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What kind of ROS2 entity is hector_object_tracker? Possible answers: 1- ROS topic, 2- ROS service, 3- ROS node.",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called hector_map_server?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What kind of ROS2 entity is hector_map_server? Possible answers: 1- ROS topic, 2- ROS service, 3- ROS node.",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called visualization_marker?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What kind of ROS2 entity is visualization_marker? Possible answers: 1- ROS topic, 2- ROS service, 3- ROS node.",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called worldmodel/image_percept?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What kind of ROS2 entity is worldmodel/image_percept? Possible answers: 1- ROS topic, 2- ROS service, 3- ROS node.",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called /hector_map_server/get_distance_to_obstacle?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What kind of ROS2 entity is /hector_map_server/get_distance_to_obstacle? Possible answers: 1- ROS topic, 2- ROS service, 3- ROS node.",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "PUBLISH",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node hector_object_tracker publish to topic visualization_marker?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SUBSCRIBE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is node hector_object_tracker subscribed to topic visualization_marker?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "PUBLISH",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node hector_object_tracker publish to topic worldmodel/image_percept?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SUBSCRIBE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is node hector_object_tracker subscribed to topic worldmodel/image_percept?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "PUBLISH",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "To which topics can node hector_object_tracker publish?",
    "answer": "visualization_marker"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SUBSCRIBE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "To which topics is node hector_object_tracker subscribed?",
    "answer": "worldmodel/image_percept"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "PUBLISH",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node hector_map_server publish to topic visualization_marker?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SUBSCRIBE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is node hector_map_server subscribed to topic visualization_marker?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "PUBLISH",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node hector_map_server publish to topic worldmodel/image_percept?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SUBSCRIBE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is node hector_map_server subscribed to topic worldmodel/image_percept?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "PUBLISH",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "To which topics can node hector_map_server publish?",
    "answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SUBSCRIBE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "To which topics is node hector_map_server subscribed?",
    "answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SERVICE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node hector_object_tracker provide service /hector_map_server/get_distance_to_obstacle?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "CLIENT",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node hector_object_tracker use service /hector_map_server/get_distance_to_obstacle as a client?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SERVICE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "Which services does node hector_object_tracker provide?",
    "answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "CLIENT",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "Which services does node hector_object_tracker use as a client?",
    "answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SERVICE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node hector_map_server provide service /hector_map_server/get_distance_to_obstacle?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "CLIENT",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node hector_map_server use service /hector_map_server/get_distance_to_obstacle as a client?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SERVICE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "Which services does node hector_map_server provide?",
    "answer": "/hector_map_server/get_distance_to_obstacle"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "CLIENT",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "Which services does node hector_map_server use as a client?",
    "answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SERVICE_TYPE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of service /hector_map_server/get_distance_to_obstacle?",
    "answer": "hector_nav_msgs/GetDistanceToObstacle"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "TOPIC_TYPE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of topic visualization_marker?",
    "answer": "visualization_msgs/Marker"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "TOPIC_TYPE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of topic worldmodel/image_percept?",
    "answer": "hector_worldmodel_msgs/ImagePercept"
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "category": "MESSAGE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a communication path from node hector_object_tracker to node hector_map_server via a topic or service?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "category": "MESSAGE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a communication path from node hector_map_server to node hector_object_tracker via a topic or service?",
    "answer": "No"
  }
]